Guide to the Jack and Rebecca Matlock Papers, 1930s-2017 RL.11082
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1980-2016; 740 items
  - Proceedings of Russian Parliament and Supreme Soviet
    - CPD-III Part III, 1990-03-14 (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0163)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0568, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0163.mp4)
    - CPD III-AM Session, 1990-03-14 (Box AV06, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0177)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0582, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0177.mp4)
    - Supreme Soviet on Glyon + Ivanov Part I, 1990-04-17 (Box AV06, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0179)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0584, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0179.mp4)
    - Supreme Soviet-Debate on Glyon + Ivanov-Part III-Also-April 18, 1990, 1990-04-17; 1990-04-18 (Box AV06, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0180)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0585, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0180.mp4)
    - RSFSR Party Congress, 1990-06-20 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0221)
    - RSFSR Party Congress part II, 1990-06-20 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0227)
    - RSFSR Party Congress, 1990-06-22 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0218)
    - RSFSR Party Congress, 1990-06-22 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0219)
    - RSFSR Party Congress Part II (To 3900), Gorbachev Replies (4615), 1990-06-22; 1990-06-23 (Box AV06, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0171)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0576, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0171.mp4)
    - 1) Время 14 July 90, 2) RSFSR Supreme Soviet 14 July 90, 3) Время 29 July 90, 4) 4 Колесо, и, 1990-07-14; 1990-07-14; 1990-07-29; 1990-07-30 (Box AV03, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0071)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0477, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0071.mp4)
    - 17 Nov 1990 Supreme Soviet-USSR Debate II PM Session, 1990-11-17 (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0150)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0555, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0150.mp4)
    - Gorbachev spech + Supreme Soviet, 1990-11-17 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0209)
    - 2) News; RSFSR CPD-II (2nd Day 1st Part, 1990-11-28 (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0140)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0545, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0140.mp4)
    - G. speech to Supreme Soviet, 1990-12 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0285)
    - News, RSFSR Debate on Priv Property, 1990-12-03 (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0145)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0550, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0145.mp4)
    - CPD RSFSR - I, 1990-12-15 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0269)
    - CPD-IV-Part I-AM Session, 1990-12-17 (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0156)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0561, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0156.mp4)
    - Gorbachev Speech to CPD IV: 1) Gorbachev on State of Union 2) CPD Discussion, 1990-12-17 (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0161)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0566, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0161.mp4)
    - Dec 18-News d, CPD IV-Day 2, Part 1, 1990-12-18 (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0142)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0547, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0142.mp4)
    - CPD IV-Day 2-Part II, 1990-12-18 (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0151)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0556, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0151.mp4)
    - Dec 19, 1990-CPD IV-Day 3, 1990-12-19 (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0147)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0552, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0147.mp4)
    - 3) December 21, 1990-CPD IV. AM Session, 4) Время, 1990-12-21 (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0139)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0544, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0139.mp4)
    - CPD IV (Pt. 2) PM Session, 1990-12-21 (Box AV06, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0172)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0577, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0172.mp4)
    - News, CPD IV, Day 6−AM Session, 1990-12-22 (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0167)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0572, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0167.mp4)
    - Dec 22, 1990 - CPD - IV - Day 6, Pt. 2; Dec 26, 1990 - News of CPD, Pt 1, 1990-12-22; 1990-12-26 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0284)
    - Dec. 26, 1990 - CPD, Pt. 11; Dec. 27, 1990 - Время with Pavlov speech and final Gorbachev speeches, 1990-12-26/1990-12-27 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0271)
    - Dec. 27 - CPD IV - Final Day, 1990-12-27 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0272)
    - RSFSR CPD, 1991-04-01 (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0153)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0558, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0153.mp4)
    - CPD RSFSR (in part) 1: to 4517, 2: from 4517, 1991-04-02; 1991-04-04 (Box AV06, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0175)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0580, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0175.mp4)
    - CPD-RSFSR (Part II), 1991-04-04 (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0166)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0571, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0166.mp4)
    - RSFSR Supreme Soviet, undated (Box AV01, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0002)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0410, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0002.mp4)
    - RSFSR−Sup. Sov., undated (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0137)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0542, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0137.mp4)
    - CPD-June 9-AM, undated (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0144)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0549, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0144.mp4)
    - CPD-June 8-PM, undated (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0148)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0553, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0148.mp4)
    - CPD III, undated (Box AV06, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0174)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0579, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0174.mp4)
  - Seminars, Forums, and Roundtables
    - TCA-88-03-31A Tape #1 Soviet Forum, Columbia University, with Jack Matlock, Robert Lequold, Marshall Shulman, and Richard Gardner, 1988-03-31 (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0359)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0359, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0362.mp3)
    - TCA-88-03-31B Tape #2 Soviet Forum, Columbia University, with Jack Matlock, Robert Lequold, Marshall Shulman, and Richard Gardner, 1988-03-31 (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0360)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0360, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0363.mp3)
    - Ambassador at Международная Жизнь, 1988-06-21 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0200)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0201, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0200.mp3)
    - Side A: Opening Magnitogorsk; Side B: Ambassador Matlock, Mrs. Matlock,, Amb. Barry Round Table with "Magnitogorsk Rabochiy" and Other Journalists, 1988-07-14; 1988-07-15 (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0354)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0354, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0357.mp3)
    - Roundtable on Cuban Missile Crisis, 1989-02-11 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0279)
    - Dostoevsky Seminar Tape I, 1990-03-07 (Box AV03, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0093)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0499, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0093.mp4)
    - Dostoevsky Seminar Tape II, 1990-03-07 (Box AV03, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0094)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0500, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0094.mp4)
    - Spaso Seminar on Dostoevsky (Взгяд), 1990-03-07 (Box AV03, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0097)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0503, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0097.mp4)
    - Spaso Seminar, Prof. John Bowlt-"Malevich and Russian Avant-Garde", 1991-03-26 (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0237)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0238, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0237.mp3)
    - Spaso Seminar-Robert Tucker & D.A. Volkogonov "Questions About Stalin", 1991-04-03 (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0236)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0237, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0236.mp3)
    - Billington Seminar, Прием в резиденции посло США at музей истории молодежного движения, 1991-05-29 (Box AV04, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0104)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0510, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0104.mp4)
    - Q + A in Salzburg, Continuation of IREX Conference in Salzburg, 1994-02-28 (Box AV18, Audio-cassette RL11082-MCS-0005)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0387, Audio-file RL11082-MCS-0011.mp3)
    - Salz Sem, 1994-06-17 (Box AV22, Audio-cassette RL11082-MCS-0050)
    - Understanding Nationalism Workshop Day 1: Opening Remarks at Reception, 1997-12-04 (Box AV18, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0376)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0376, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0379.mp3)
    - Understanding Nationalism Workshop Day 2: Tape 4, 1997-12-05 (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0374)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0374, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0377.mp3)
    - Understanding Nationalism Workshop Day 2: Tape 3, 1997-12-05 (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0375)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0375, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0378.mp3)
    - Understanding Nationalism Workshop Day 2: Tape 1, 1997-12-05 (Box AV18, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0377)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0377, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0380.mp3)
    - Understanding Nationalism Workshop Day 2: Tape 2, 1997-12-05 (Box AV18, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0378)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0378, Audio-file RL11082-MCS-0001.mp3)
    - Understanding Nationalism Workshop Day 3 Tape 1, 1997-12-06 (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0373)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0373, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0376.mp3)
    - Seminar with Billington, Seminar and Questions and Answers, undated (Box AV07, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0007)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0008, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0007.mp3)
    - Billington Seminar, undated (Box AV07, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0025)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0026, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0025.mp3)
    - Billington Q & A, undated (Box AV07, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0026)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0027, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0026.mp3)
    - Spaso Seminar on Federalism: Dr. Eric Hoffman and Boris Topornin, undated (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0350)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0350, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0353.mp3)
    - Spaso Seminar on Federalism: After dinner discussion, undated (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0351)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0351, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0354.mp3)
  - Town Meetings
    - Town Meeting, 1990-08-06 (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0370)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0370, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0373.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock's Town Meeting, 1990-11-14 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0164)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0165, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0164.mp3)
    - Town Meeting, January 17, 1991 12:00 Noon, 1991-01-17 (Box AV07, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0001)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0002, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0001.mp3)
    - Town Meeting, 1991-02-25 (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0230)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0231, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0230.mp3)
    - Ambassador's Town Meeting, 1991-03-20 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0239)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0240, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0239.mp3)
    - Amb.'s Town Meeting, 1991-03-29 (Box AV10, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0136)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0137, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0136.mp3)
    - Ambassador's Town Meeting, 1991-04-03 (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0238)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0239, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0238.mp3)
    - Amb. Matlock, Mtg. with Students from Институт Молодежди (Institut Molodyozhi) at Spaso House, 1991-04-29 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0139)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0140, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0139.mp3)
    - Amb. Matlock's Town Meeting, 1991-05-08 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0142)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0143, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0142.mp3)
    - JFM Town Meeting in DOB re: Gulf Military Action, undated (Box AV07, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0005)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0006, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0005.mp3)
  - Miscellaneous audiovisual
    - TJOM-LANY, 1982-03-07 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0293)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0294, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0296.mp3)
    - VOA-Czechoslovak Svc. Including Bohemia Communist Svcs. toward Side 1, TAC-82-05-16, 1982-05-16 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0283)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0284, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0284.mp3)
    - Travel Notes, TAC-82-10-11, 1982-10-11 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0281)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0282, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0282.mp3)
    - New Year's Greetings for VOA Czechosl. Svc., TAC-83-01-01, 1983-01-01 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0278)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0279, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0279.mp3)
    - Side 1: Amb. Matlock VOA CZECH, Side 2: VOA-CZECH, 1983-03-07; 1982-03-23 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0294)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0295, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0297.mp3)
    - Inside Russia: Billy Graham, 1984 (Box AV02, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0064)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0470, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0064.mp4)
    - Christmas 1984 I& II, TAC-84-12-25A, 1984-12-25 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0276)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0277, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0277.mp3)
    - Xmas 1984 Part 3, TAC-84-12-25B, 1984-12-25 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0277)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0278, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0278.mp3)
    - NY + Co-Jack Matlock, 1985-11-20 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0264)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0265, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0265.mp3)
    - Matlock - Greensboro Interview, 1987-02-28 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0210)
    - "New Ambassador" Peter Arnett Arnett Pkg., CNN Moscow, TY/Moscow, 1987-04-29 (Box AV06, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0134)
    - Amb + Flam for VOA Russian, 1987-06-09 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0300)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0300, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0303.mp3)
    - Rostov on Don [Dom Kino?], 1987-10 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0208)
    - Moscow, Nov. 7 (Rev. Day 70th anniversary), Red Square Parade 1987, 1987-11-07 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0224)
    - Tbilisi, trip to open "Information USA", 1987-12-16/1987-12-17 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0247)
    - The Trip of President Reagan to the Moscow Summit, 1988 (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0299)
    - Moscow, Celebration of 30th Anniversary Exchange Agreement, 1988-01-27 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0207)
    - National Geographic Special "Inside the Soviet Circus", 1988-02-04 (Box AV02, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0063)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0469, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0063.mp4)
    - Tashkent, 1988-02-25/1988-02-26 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0248)
    - Brugling of CFR Group Side One, 1988-04-18 (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0361)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0361, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0364.mp3)
    - Время and Reagan interview with Soviet TV, 1988-05-28 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0222)
    - Время CNN Spaso House Bit, 1988-05-29 (Box AV03, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0081)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0487, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0081.mp4)
    - President Reagan's arrival in Moscow and opening remarks in Kremlin, 1988-05-29 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0223)
    - Время, 1988-05-30 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0259)
    - Vremya, Spaso Reciprocal dinner, 1988-05-31 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0257)
    - 1.6.88 Время and Gorbachev's press conference, 1988-06-01 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0260)
    - 1.6.88, Pres. Reagan's Press Conference; 2.6.88, Время and Gorb. Meeting w/social activists, 1988-06-01; 1988-06-02 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0256)
    - Party Conference-1 July 1988-Part II, Лигачев, Горбачев, 1988-07-01 (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0146)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0551, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0146.mp4)
    - IXIX Party Conf-July 1, 1988 Part I, (Елцин) At end: Conclusion Vote on Res), 1988-07-01 (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0149)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0554, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0149.mp4)
    - TVN-88-07-3/4, 1988-07-03/1988-07-04 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0240)
    - Vladimir/Suzdal, July 9-10, 1988; Moscow, Aug. 6, 1988, 1988-07-09/1988-07-10; 1988-08-06 (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0292)
    - Amb. Matlock, 1988-08-26 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0187)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0188, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0187.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock, 1988-09-03 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0183)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0184, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0183.mp3)
    - Gorbachev in Norilsk, 1988-09-14 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0264)
    - Jacoby/Storm Productions, "A walk in the woods" demo reel, NY, Wash, London, Moscow, 1988-10-03 (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0291)
    - Booneville, TN, 1988-11-13 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0236)
    - Segment-Modern Maturity, Lucille Lortel, 1988-12-16 (Box AV02, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0034)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0441, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0034.mp4)
    - "Before and After Midnight" with the Matlocks, 1988-12-24 (Box AV04, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0103)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0509, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0103.mp4)
    - MSG & RR New Years msg, 1989-01-01 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0232)
    - Trostnikov,Viktor Re Spaso Archicture, 1989-03-02 (Box AV07, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0030)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0031, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0030.mp3)
    - Amb Matlock at Dom Kino--"Beaches", 1989-03-24 (Box AV08, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0068)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0069, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0068.mp3)
    - Mike Joyce with Beecher May 15, 1989, and Amb. Matlock with Bill Beecher May 17, 1989, 1989-05-15; 1989-05-17 (Box AV09, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0081)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0082, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0081.mp3)
    - Amb. w/ Bill Beecher, May 17-Part II, 1989-05-17 (Box AV09, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0082)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0083, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0082.mp3)
    - Время on CPD- June 1 and Время News-June 4, 1989-06-01; 1989-06-04 (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0165)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0570, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0165.mp4)
    - untitled, 1989-06-27 or or 1989-07-04 (but most likely the 4th) (Box AV04, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0130)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0536, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0130.mp4)
    - Vremya, Ambassador Matlock's remarks, 1989-07-04 (Box AV03, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0100)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0506, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0100.mp4)
    - Camera, 1989-08-12; 1990-05-01; 1990-05-09 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0288)
    - Лит-Худож видео канал-I, -II, Solzhenitsyn atend-III, 1989-08-16 (Box AV02, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0050)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0456, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0050.mp4)
    - Television-Revolution in a Box - no audio, 1989-09-13 (Box AV04, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0129)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0535, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0129.mp4)
    - Report on visit to Katyn (Soviet TV - Время), 1989-10-30 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0182)
    - Gorbachev - TV interview, from Soviet TV, 1989-11 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0263)
    - Matlock, 1989-11-03 (Box AV10, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0125)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0126, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0125.mp3)
    - Matlock, Sov. Journs., 1989-11-09 (Box AV08, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0050)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0051, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0050.mp3)
    - Supreme Soviet AM, 1989-11-27 (Box AV04, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0106)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0512, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0106.mp4)
    - Voznesensky, 1989-12 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0261)
    - "Aktual'noye Interview" Dec. 1, 1989 as played to Supreme Soviet, 1989-12-01 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0289)
    - 10 Dec 89 - 7Дней; 11 Dec 89 - Время, 1989-12-10, 1989-12-11 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0214)
    - Sakharov Funeral and Tribute, 1989-12-18 (Box AV03, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0084)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0490, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0084.mp4)
    - 1) Pasternak Evening, 3) Gubenko, 4) Aksyonov/380_, 1989-12-27 (Box AV03, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0083)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0489, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0083.mp4)
    - Solouklein, 1990-01 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0287)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0288, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0289.mp3)
    - Gorbachev in Lithuania, 1990-01 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0225)
    - Время, 10 January 1990; Romeo and Juliet, 1990-01-10 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0217)
    - [Title TBD], 1990-01-15 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0211)
    - Rebecca's Photo Exhibit; Gorbachev on Azer., 1990-01-19; 1990-01-20 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0286)
    - Menshikov mansion; news, 1990-01-21 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0230)
    - Время, 1990-01-22/1990-01-25 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0220)
    - Supreme Soviet Debate on Baltic Ecomomic Autonomy, 1990-02 (Box AV03, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0089)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0495, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0089.mp4)
    - Matlock w/ Baklanov, 1990-02-02 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0251)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0252, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0251.mp3)
    - Supreme Soviet, 1990-02-26 (Box AV03, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0087)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0493, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0087.mp4)
    - 1) 27 Feb 90-Vote on Pres. System, 2) 6 Mar 90-7 Дней, 1990-02-27; 1990-03-06 (Box AV03, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0092)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0498, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0092.mp4)
    - Matlock with Aleksey Karavlov at Spaso, 1990-03-03 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0253)